A Guide to the Robert N. Giaimo Papers 1980.0003
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series V: Outgoing Correspondence, 1959-1980
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1965 (Box 141:, Folder 4616)
    - F - G, 1970 (Box 149:, Folder 5063-5069)
    - Gp - Gz, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5070)
    - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5071)
    - General Services Administration (GSA), 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5072)
    - Guilford, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5073)
    - H, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5074-5077)
    - Hamden, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5078)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5079)
    - House of Representatives, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5080)
    - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5081)
    - I, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5082)
    - Immigration, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5083)
    - Interior, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5084)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5085)
    - J, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5086)
    - Justice, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5087)
    - K - L, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5088-5094)
    - Labor, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5095)
    - Library of Congress, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5096)
    - M, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5097-5103)
    - Madison, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5104)
    - Marine Corps, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5105)
    - Milford, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5106)
    - N, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5107-5108)
    - Navy, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5109)
    - New Haven, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5110)
    - North Haven, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5111)
    - North Branford, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5112)
    - O, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5113)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5114)
    - Orange, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5115)
    - P, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5116-5119)
    - Post Office, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5120)
    - Q - S, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5121-5130)
    - Selective Service, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5131)
    - Senate, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5132)
    - Social Security Administration (SSA), 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5133)
    - State, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5134)
    - Stratford, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5135)
    - Ta - Ti, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5136)
    - Transportation, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5137)
    - Treasury, 1970 (Box 150:, Folder 5138)
    - Tu - V, 1970 (Box 151:, Folder 5139-5141)
    - Veterans Administration (VA), 1970 (Box 151:, Folder 5142)
    - W, 1970 (Box 151:, Folder 5143-5145)
    - West Haven, 1970 (Box 151:, Folder 5146)
    - Woodbridge, 1970 (Box 151:, Folder 5147)
    - X - Z, 1970 (Box 151:, Folder 5148-5149)
    - A, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5150-5153)
    - Agriculture, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5154)
    - Air Force, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5155)
    - Architect, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5156)
    - Army, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5157)
    - B, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5158-5165)
    - Branford, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5166)
    - C, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5167-5173)
    - Civil Service, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5174)
    - Coast Guard, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5175)
    - Commerce, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5176)
    - Committees, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5177)
    - Connecticut, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5178)
    - Consuls, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5179)
    - D, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5180-5184)
    - D.C. Government, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5185)
    - Defense, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5186)
    - E, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5187)
    - East Haven, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5188)
    - Environmental Quality Control, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5189)
    - Executive Office, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5190)
    - F, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5191-5196)
    - Federal Agencies, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5197)
    - G, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5198-5201)
    - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5202)
    - General Services Administration (GSA), 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5203)
    - Guilford, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5204)
    - H, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5205-5209)
    - Hamden, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5210)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5211)
    - House of Representatives, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5212)
    - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5213)
    - I, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5214)
    - Immigration, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5215)
    - Interior, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5216)
    - Interstate Commerce, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5217)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5218)
    - Ja - Jn, 1971 (Box 151:, Folder 5219)
    - Jo - Jz, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5220)
    - Justice, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5221)
    - K - L, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5222-5231)
    - Labor, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5232)
    - Library of Congress, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5233)
    - M, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5234-5241)
    - Madison, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5242)
    - Marine Corps, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5243)
    - Milford, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5244)
    - N, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5245-5246)
    - Navy, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5247)
    - New Haven, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5248)
    - North Branford, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5249)
    - North Haven, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5250)
    - O, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5251)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5252)
    - Orange, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5253)
    - P, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5254-5258)
    - Post Office, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5259)
    - Q - S, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5260-5271)
    - Selective Service, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5272)
    - Social Security Administration (SSA), 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5273)
    - State, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5274)
    - Stratford, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5275)
    - T, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5276-5277)
    - Transportation, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5278)
    - Treasury, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5279)
    - U - V, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5280-5281)
    - W, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5282-5284)
    - West Haven, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5285)
    - Woodbridge, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5286)
    - X - Z, 1971 (Box 152:, Folder 5287-5288)
    - A, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5289-5293)
    - Agriculture, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5294)
    - Air Force, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5295)
    - Architect, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5296)
    - Army, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5297)
    - B, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5298-5303)
    - Branford, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5304)
    - C, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5305-5311)
    - Civil Service, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5312)
    - Clinton, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5313)
    - Coast Guard, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5314)
    - Commerce, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5315)
    - Committees, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5316)
    - Connecticut, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5317)
    - Consuls, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5318)
    - D, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5319-5322)
    - D.C. Government, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5323)
    - Defense, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5324)
    - E, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5325)
    - East Haven, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5326)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5327)
    - Executive Office, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5328)
    - F, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5329-5334)
    - Federal Agencies, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5335)
    - G, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5336-5339)
    - Government Accounting and Printing Offices, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5340)
    - General Services Administration (GSA), 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5341)
    - Guilford, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5342)
    - H, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5343-5347)
    - Hamden, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5348)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5349)
    - House of Representatives, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5350)
    - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5351)
    - I, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5352)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5353)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5354)
    - Interior, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5355)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5356)
    - J, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5357-5358)
    - Justice, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5359)
    - Ka - Kh, 1972 (Box 153:, Folder 5360-5361)
    - Ki - Kz, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5362-5363)
    - Killingworth, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5364)
    - L, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5365-5369)
    - Labor, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5370)
    - Library of Congress, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5371)
    - M, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5372-5379)
    - Madison, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5380)
    - Marine Corps, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5381)
    - Milford, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5382)
    - N, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5383-5385)
    - NASA, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5386)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities and Arts, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5387)
    - National Science Foundation, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5388)
    - Navy, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5389)
    - New Haven, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5390)
    - North Branford, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5391)
    - North Haven, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5392)
    - O, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5393)
    - Orange, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5394)
    - OEO/OEP, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5395)
    - P, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5396-5401)
    - Postal Service, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5402)
    - Price Commission, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5403)
    - Q - S, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5404-5415)
    - Selective Service, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5416)
    - Senate, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5417)
    - Social Security Administrative (SSA), 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5418)
    - State, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5419)
    - Stratford, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5420)
    - T, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5421-5422)
    - Transportation, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5423)
    - Treasury, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5424)
    - U - V, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5425-5426)
    - Veterans Administration (VA), 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5427)
    - Wa - Wm, 1972 (Box 154:, Folder 5428-5429)
    - Wn - Wz, 1972 (Box 155:, Folder 5430-5431)
    - Wallingford, 1972 (Box 155:, Folder 5432)
    - West Haven, 1972 (Box 155:, Folder 5433)
    - Woodbridge, 1972 (Box 155:, Folder 5434)
    - X - Z, 1972 (Box 155:, Folder 5435-5436)
    - A, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5437-5441)
    - ACTION, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5442)
    - Agriculture, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5443)
    - Air Force, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5444)
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Commissioner, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5445)
    - Amtrak, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5446)
    - Architect, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5447)
    - Army, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5448)
    - Army Corps of Engineers, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5449)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (AEC), 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5450)
    - B, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5451-5457)
    - Botanical Gardens, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5458)
    - Branford, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5459)
    - Bureau of Prisons, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5460)
    - Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco and Firearms (ATF), 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5461)
    - C, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5462-5467)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5468)
    - Civil Service, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5469)
    - Clinton, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5470)
    - Coast Guard, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5471)
    - Commerce, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5472)
    - Commission on Civil Rights, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5473)
    - Committees, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5474)
    - Connecticut Officials, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5475)
    - Consuls, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5476)
    - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5477)
    - Cost of Living Council, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5478)
    - Customs Bureau, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5479)
    - D, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5480-5484)
    - Defense, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5485)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5486)
    - E, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5487)
    - East Haven, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5488)
    - Economic Development Administration, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5489)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5490)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC), 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5491)
    - Executive Office, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5492)
    - F, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5493-5498)
    - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5499)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5500)
    - Federal Communication Commission, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5501)
    - Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC), 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5502)
    - Federal Energy Office, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5503)
    - Federal Highway Administration, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5504)
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5505)
    - Federal Maritime Commission, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5506)
    - Federal Reserve Board, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5507)
    - Federal Telecommunications System, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5508)
    - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5509)
    - Food and Drug Administration (FDA), 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5510)
    - Ge - Gi, 1973 (Box 155:, Folder 5511)
    - Gj - Gz, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5512-5514)
    - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5515)
    - General Services Administration (GSA), 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5516)
    - Government Printing Office (GPO), 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5517)
    - Guilford, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5518)
    - H, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5519-5523)
    - Hamden, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5524)
    - House of Representatives, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5525)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5526)
    - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5527)
    - I, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5528)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5529)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5530)
    - Interior, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5531)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5532)
    - J, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5533-5534)
    - Justice, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5535)
    - K, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5536-5539)
    - Killingworth, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5540)
    - L, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5541-5545)
    - Labor, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5546)
    - Library of Congress, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5547)
    - M, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5548-5554)
    - Madison, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5555)
    - Marine Corps, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5556)
    - Milford, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5557)
    - N, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5558-5559)
    - NASA, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5560)
    - National Guard, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5561)
    - National Mediation Board, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5562)
    - National Science Foundation, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5563)
    - Navy, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5564)
    - New Haven, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5565)
    - North Branford, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5566)
    - O, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5567)
    - OEO/OEP, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5568)
    - Orange, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5569)
    - P - Ph, 1973 (Box 156:, Folder 5570-5572)
    - Pi - Pz, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5573-5575)
    - Patent Office, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5576)
    - Postal Service, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5577)
    - Price Commission, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5578)
    - Public Health Service, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5579)
    - Q - R, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5580-5585)
    - Railroad Retirement Board, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5586)
    - S, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5587-5592)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5593)
    - Selective Service, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5594)
    - Senate, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5595)
    - Small Business Administration (SBA), 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5596)
    - Smithsonian, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5597)
    - Social Security Administration (SSA), 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5598)
    - State, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5599)
    - Stratford, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5600)
    - T, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5601-5602)
    - Tariff Commission, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5603)
    - Transportation, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5604)
    - Treasury, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5605)
    - U, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5606)
    - U.S. Information Agency, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5607)
    - United Nations, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5608)
    - V, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5609)
    - Veterans Administration (VA), 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5610)
    - W, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5611-5613)
    - Wallingford, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5614)
    - West Haven, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5615)
    - White House, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5616)
    - Woodbridge, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5617)
    - X - Z, 1973 (Box 157:, Folder 5618-5619)
    - A, 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5620-5624)
    - ACTION, 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5625)
    - Agriculture, 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5626)
    - Air Force, 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5627)
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Commissioner, 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5628)
    - Amtrak, 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5629)
    - Architect, 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5630)
    - Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5631)
    - Army, 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5632)
    - Army Corps of Engineers, 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5633)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (AEC), 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5634)
    - B, 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5635-5643)
    - Botanical Gardens, 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5644)
    - Branford, 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5645)
    - Bureau of Prisons, 1974 (Box 157:, Folder 5646)
    - C, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5647-5654)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5655)
    - Civil Service, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5656)
    - Clinton, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5657)
    - Coast Guard, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5658)
    - Commerce, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5659)
    - Commission on Civil Rights, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5660)
    - Committees, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5661)
    - Connecticut Officials, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5662)
    - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5663)
    - Cost of Living Council, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5664)
    - Consuls, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5665)
    - Customs Bureau, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5666)
    - D, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5667-5673)
    - Defense, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5674)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5675)
    - D.C. Government, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5676)
    - E, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5677)
    - East Haven, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5678)
    - Economic Development Administration, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5679)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5680)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5681)
    - Executive Office, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5682)
    - F, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5683-5688)
    - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5689)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5690)
    - Federal Commerce Commission, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5691)
    - Federal Deposit Insurance Commission (FDIC), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5692)
    - Federal Energy Office, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5693)
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5694)
    - Federal Maritime Commission, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5695)
    - Federal Power Commission, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5696)
    - Federal Register, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5697)
    - Federal Reserve Board, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5698)
    - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5699)
    - Food and Drug Administration (FDA), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5700)
    - G, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5701-5707)
    - Government Accounting Office (GAO), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5708)
    - Government Printing Office (GPO), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5709)
    - General Services Administration (GSA), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5710)
    - Guilford, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5711)
    - H, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5712-5718)
    - Hamden, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5719)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5720)
    - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5721)
    - House of Representatives, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5722)
    - I, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5723)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5724)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5725)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5726)
    - Interior, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5727)
    - J, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5728-5730)
    - Justice, 1974 (Box 158:, Folder 5731)
    - K, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5732-5736)
    - Killingworth, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5737)
    - L, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5738-5744)
    - Labor, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5745)
    - Library of Congress, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5746)
    - M, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5747-5754)
    - Madison, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5755)
    - Marine Corps, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5756)
    - Milford, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5757)
    - N, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5758-5760)
    - NASA, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5761)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5762)
    - National Guard, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5763)
    - National Mediation Board, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5764)
    - National Science Foundation, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5765)
    - Navy, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5766)
    - New Haven, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5767)
    - North Branford, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5768)
    - North Haven, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5769)
    - O, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5770-5771)
    - OEO/OEP, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5772)
    - Office of Management and Budget (OMB), 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5773)
    - Orange, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5774)
    - P, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5775-5782)
    - Postal Service, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5783)
    - Q, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5784-5790)
    - Railroad Retirement Board, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5791)
    - S, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5792-5804)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5805)
    - Selective Service, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5806)
    - Senate, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5807)
    - Small Business Administration (SBA), 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5808)
    - Smithsonian, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5809)
    - Social Security Administration (SSA), 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5810)
    - State, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5811)
    - Stratford, 1974 (Box 159:, Folder 5812)
    - T, 1974 (Box 160:, Folder 5813-5815)
    - Transportation, 1974 (Box 160:, Folder 5816)
    - Treasury, 1974 (Box 160:, Folder 5817)
    - U, 1974 (Box 160:, Folder 5818)
    - United Nations, 1974 (Box 160:, Folder 5819)
    - V, 1974 (Box 160:, Folder 5820-5821)
    - Veterans Administration (VA), 1974 (Box 160:, Folder 5822)
    - W, 1974 (Box 160:, Folder 5823-5827)
    - Wallingford, 1974 (Box 160:, Folder 5828)
    - West Haven, 1974 (Box 160:, Folder 5829)
    - Woodbridge, 1974 (Box 160:, Folder 5830)
    - White House, 1974 (Box 160:, Folder 5831)
    - X - Z, 1974 (Box 160:, Folder 5832-5833)
    - A, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5834-5838)
    - ACTION, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5839)
    - Agriculture, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5840)
    - Air Force, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5841)
    - Alcohol, Tobacco and Firearms (ATF), 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5842)
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Commissioner, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5843)
    - Amtrak, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5844)
    - Architect, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5845)
    - Archives, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5846)
    - Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5847)
    - Army, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5848)
    - Army Corps of Engineers, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5849)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (AEC), 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5850)
    - B, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5851-59)
    - Botanical Gardens, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5860)
    - Branford, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5861)
    - C, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5862-5870)
    - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5871)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5872)
    - Civil Service Commission, 1975 (Box 160:, Folder 5873)